To create a new translation you should:

- Create a copy of "Default.lng". This file contains all English text definitions.
- Translate all text definitions in the copied file. You can simply use Notepad.
- The ODTranslateAid.exe can be used to help with the translating, but it requires the .NET 2.0 Framework
  runtimes be installed. http://www.microsoft.com/downloads/details.aspx?FamilyID=0856eacb-4362-4b0d-8edd-aab15c5e04f5&displaylang=en
- If not using the TrandlationAid helper program, the .lng file can be edited by hand. However,
  **be sure to carefully follow the instructions listed in the top of the .lng file when editing the .lng file manually.**
- We suggest adding your name and email address to a comment at the top of the file. Comment
  lines must start with ; 
- Change the selected language in ObjectDock settings.
- If you would like your new .lng file to be included with future ObjectDock updates,
  please send a copy to kwilas@stardock.com. 
- If you have problems, feel free to contact support@stardock.com.


